Hi guys, welcome to another video here on my channel and I have to introduce you to my newest boots
number 318 by Fernando Berlin, crotch high over knees and I thought I'm going to show you some
styling ideas with them. I posted a picture from the time I visited Fernando in his showroom in
through and somebody asked what do you wear with these kind of shoes because
they're so long so I have some ideas and I'm going to show them to you since I
already squeezed into this jumpsuit you may remember from a jumpsuit up I'm
going to put them on and see how this works together
I was just so far from here
Focused on my own way
Without ever looking back
To those who lived in fear
There was nothing I could do
There was nothing you said
that could make me realize how much lucky I was
Okay, to be honest, this is not the best combination.
Yeah, the jumpsuit was simply for the intro and I wanted to try this, but let's quickly change into the outfits I really planned for this video.
Super classy, I love this combination a lot.
It's a Swedish collar, um, collar, obviously, and corset, story corset,
And I think the loose fit jumpsuit makes a great look together with the tight boots.
Next outfit, I love this green color, it's colorful but not too bright
and paired it with some leather, fake leather pants
important is that the shorts are not too long so there has to be a slight gap between the boots and the shorts
Did you know that I have another pair of banana balloon boots?
These ones.
So I'm going to show you one outfit with them really quick and then I'm going to change
back to these ones.
It's the perfect concert or festival outfit with the flat boots, leather jacket and a
band shirt, in this case it's Fede hat. And this is just so comfy. Oh, I forgot the new
Paradise Thermo leggings. Still love them. They work well together with the shoes and
everything. I like this outfit. It's so comfy. I wanna go to concert. Anyway, up to the next
outfit. Yeah, so that's the party outfit. I absolutely wanted to do an outfit with a
short skirt and I found this one by FACE on my clothing pile and I think this does look
pretty good together.
Didn't expect it.
Also the top.
Bright and cool.
Moving on to another more classy outfit.
So this is the more like cold weather outfit for winter with the jacket and leather leggings
do look great with the boots and I put on my booty pants, no, boot bands and Swarovski
crystal bands whatever to push up the boots a bit more.
It looks great together and it sparkles and some other accessories make the look.
I was so dumb and not out of touch
I was so wrong, I was so bad
I was so bad
Okay, so this is a combination by Lohr Handmade.
Still love this jacket.
And the bodysuit.
So kind of shorts, top combination again, but it's one piece.
It looks great together with the boots. The fabric really works together well.
Okay, I hope I could give you some impressions and styling ideas and a lot of boot content.
I really love these ones. I have to say thank you to George who gifted them to me.
Thank you so much, they're great. Love them so much and I think they're so elegant.
By the way I'm wearing them made to measure. I think shoe size is 38 in these
ones the other ones are 40. A bit weird but yeah I hope you had fun see you at the next video bye